Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory7 Mss.B.B61.inventory07
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents K
  - Keppel, Frederick P. (Box 50)
    - F.P. Keppel -- from E.S. Delich, 1906 Aug. 16
    - F.P. Keppel -- from H.M. Dietrick, 1906 Aug. 13
    - F.P. Keppel -- from N.D. Harris, 1907 Feb. 1
    - F.P. Keppel -- from C.B. Hurst, 1906 Aug. 17
    - F.P. Keppel -- from M.W. Ireland, 1918 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - F.P. Keppel -- from W.G. Leland, 1928 Apr. 1
    - (Enc. originally with Leland, W.G. to Boas, F. & Kent, R.G. Apr. 18, 1928), 1928 Apr. 19
    - (Enc. originally with Leland, W.G. to Boas, F. & Kent, R.G., Apr. 18, 1928)
    - F.P. Keppel -- from J. Nash, 1909 Apr. 14
    - F.P. Keppel -- from F. Osborn, 1939 Oct. 13
    - (Enc. with Osborn, F., Oct. 13, 1939)
    - F.P. Keppel -- from A.K. Parker, 1906 Sept. 6
    - F.P. Keppel -- from Hoffman Phily, 1906 Aug. 24
    - F.P. Keppel -- from S. Smith, 1906 Aug. 27
    - F.P. Keppel -- from A.M. Tozzer, 1933 Mar. 21
    - (Enc. with Tozzer, A.M., Mar. 21, 1933)
    - F.P. Keppel -- from E.B. Walker, 1906 Aug. 20
    - F.P. Keppel -- from Ethelbert Watts, 1906 Aug. 13
    - F.P. Keppel -- from J.H. Worman, 1906 June 13
  - Keppler, Rudolph (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1904 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 5; 1p.
  - Kerkhof, Franz (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - (Enc: Kerkhof to Reichsministerium des Innern Haas to Akademie der Wissenschaften im Wien), 1932 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - F. Kerkhof -- to Reichsministerium des Innern
      - (See Enc: Kerkhof, Franz, Aug. 9,1932)
  - Kerkhof, Karl (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - See Villard, O.G., Oct. 6, 1922.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - K. Kerkhof -- from L.E.J. Brouwer, 1922 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - K. Kerkhof -- from F.F. Bunker, 1932 Dec. 29
  - Kern, M.E. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 10; 1p.
  - Kern, P.J. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct.; telegram
    - To Boas
      - See Dearborn, N.H., Sept. 24, 1938.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 29; 1p.
  - Kerney, J.L. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 2
  - Kertesz, V. (Box 51)
    - V. Kertesz -- to U.S. Dept. of Justice, 1917 Nov. 1
  - Kessler, Charles N. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - C.N. Kessler -- to Amer. Folk Lore, 1918 Apr. 14; 2p.
  - Kessler, L. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 13; 2p.
  - Kewinski, Karl von (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 18; 1p.
  - Key, W.S. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 2; 2p.
  - Khüler?? (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1923 July 12; 2p.
  - Kidder, A.V. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 June 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 June 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 July 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 May 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 July 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 25; 1p.
    - (Enc: List of those to whom invitation to meeting was sent.), 1927 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 June 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - A.V. Kidder -- to National Research Council Div. of Anthropology & Psychology. Comm. on a study of the American Negro, 1926 Oct. 30; 3p.
    - A.V. Kidder -- from E.R. Riesen, 1931 Apr. 21
    - A.V. Kidder -- to E.R. Riesen, 1931 Apr. 27; 2p.
  - Kiemnenhuis??, A.W. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 27; 4p.
  - Kienast, F. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 15; 2p.
  - Kiepert, Heinrich (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1887 June 6
    - To Boas, 1887 July 1
    - To Boas, 1887 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1887 Oct. 9; card
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 13; card
  - Kieran, J.M. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 14; 1p.
  - Kiess, E. -- (see also Riess) (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 30; 1p.
  - Kiess, Walter (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 17; postcard
  - Kihn, Mrs. W.L. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 13; 1p.
  - Kiliani, Otto T.G. (Box 51)
    - O.T.G. Kiliani -- to Emil L. Boas, 1904 June 18; 2p.
  - Kilmuensheim,? A.W. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 17; 2p.
  - Kilpatrick, William H. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1932 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 4; 2p.
    - See Lindeman, E.O June 26, 1936., 1937 Sept. 4; telegr.
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938.
  - Kimball, Charles O. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 17
  - Kimme, A. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 19
  - Kimme, C. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1893 Aug. 26; 3p.
  - Kinckiner, R.A. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 1p.
  - Kindervater, A.E. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 28; 2p.
  - Kindler, G.E. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 3; 2p.
  - Kine, B. DeM.? (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 5; 1p.
  - King, A.A. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 20; 2p.
  - King, A.N. (Box 51)
    - Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 26; 2p.
  - King, A.V. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 17
  - King, B. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 10; 1p.
  - King, Carol (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec.; 1p.
  - King, F.M. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 1
  - King, Irving (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 10
  - King, L.E. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1926 July 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 July 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 23; telegr.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 17; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 21; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 23; 1p.
  - King, Marguerite (Box 51)
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), Nov. 6, 1941.
  - King, W.H. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1936 July 14; 1p.
  - Kingdon, Frank (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 19; 1p.
  - Kingsbury, John Adams (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 13; 1p.
  - Kingsbury, S.M. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 16; 1p.
  - Kingsford, H.S. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 24
  - Kinkead, Marjorie (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 22; 1p.
  - Kinnicutt, Elenora (Mrs. Francis P.) (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 May 25; 4p.
  - Kinnicutt, Francis P. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 end; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 end; 3p.
    - F.P. Kinnicutt -- from Ann M. Carpenter, 1906; 4p.
  - Kirby, T.E. (Box 51)
    - T.E. Kirby -- from B. Laufer, 1905 Jan. 11
    - T.E. Kirby -- from B. Laufer, 1905 Jan. 23
  - Kirchhoff, Alfred (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1885 July 7
    - To Boas, 1885 July 11; postcard
    - To Boas, 1885 July 20; postcard
    - To Boas, 1885 July 29
      - see P. Kirchhoff, 1886 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1886 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 13; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1896 June 6; 4p.
  - Kirchhoff, F. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 28
  - Kirchhoff, Paul (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 July 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 July 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 7; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 27; 10p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 July 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 30; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 31; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 June 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 July 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 27; 3p.
    - P. Kirchhoff -- from G. Bezold, 1886 Feb. 20
    - P. Kirchhoff -- from Gt. Brit. Undersecretary of State for Colonial Affairs, 1932 Feb. 15
    - P. Kirchhoff -- to Gt. Brit. Under Secretary of State for the Colonies, 1932 Jan. 28; 1p.
  - Kirchwey, Freda (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 2; 1p.
  - Kirkhof (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 21; 1p.
  - Kirkus, V. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 7; 1p.
  - Kirtland, Grace E. (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1894 Nov. 7
  - Kisch, Guido (Box 51)
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec.; 7p.
  - Kissel, Edgar C. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Sept. 22; 3p.
  - Kissell, Mary Lois (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 end
  - Kittin, S.S.A. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 21; 1p.
  - Kittredge, Tracy (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1941 Sept. 18; 1p.
  - Kittridge, George L. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1909 May 19
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 6
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1917 May 25
    - From Boas, 1917 June 14
    - From Boas, 1917 June 14
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 June 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1909 May 17
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1913 May 4
    - To Boas, 1913 May 15
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 27; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1914 May 17; 6p. (incompl.)
    - To Boas, 1915 June 15; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - G.L. Kittridge -- to H.A. Andrews, 1913 June 3; 14p.
  - Kjersmeier, Carl (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 29; 1p.
  - Kjesbu, N. (Box 51)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 14; 1p.
  - Klaatsch
    - To Boas, 1923?
  - Klaeber, Fr. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 May 10; 2p.
  - Klapper, Paul (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 18; 1p.
      (Enc: Bilden, P. Race and culture in the New World. Outline)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas
      - See Prokosch, E., Sept. 11, 1933.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 8; 2p.
  - Klare, H.W. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Klasky, Elwa H. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 28; 1p.
  - Kleber, C.C. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 9; 1p.
  - Kleeck, Mary van (Box 52)
    - See Brewster, Dorothy, July 18, 1939.
  - Klein, C.H. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
  - Klein, Daniel (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 20; 1p.
  - Klein, F. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 20; 1p.
  - Klein, Philip (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 25; 1p.
  - Klemperer, P. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 6; 2p.
  - Klenze, Camillo von (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec.; 2p.
    - See F_ehn, R. to Mitglieder..., Nov. 1931
    - To Boas, 1933 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 25; 1p.
    - C. Klenze -- to Otto F. Schmidt, 1931 Aug. 18
    - (Enc: Busse, Gisela von, Aug. 2, 1931)
  - Klineberg, Otto (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 June 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 June 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - On margin: Liberman, Maurice, 1938 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1939 June 6; 1p.
    - To Boas
      - See Boas, F. to Social science research council, Nov. 26, 1926.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 6; 10p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 8; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 16; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 27; 3p.
    - See Boas, F. to Columbia Univ. Council for research in the social sciences, 1929 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 18; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 24; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 15; 4p.
    - See Boas, F., Dec. 3, 1931.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 24; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec.; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July
    - O. Klineberg -- from Z.N. Hurston, 1929 Oct. 22
    - O. Klineberg -- from F. Lorimer, 1933 Jan. 9; telegr.
  - Klingenheben (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 4; 1p.
  - KlodiD, R. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 14; 4p.
  - Klopfer, Bruno (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec.
    - See enc. Boas, F. to Moe, H.A., Dec. 31, 1936.
    - B. Klopfer -- to N.A. Dayton, 1936 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - B. Klopfer -- to Benjamin Malzberg, 1936 June 22; 1p.
    - B. Klopfer -- to Benjamin Malzberg, 1936 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - B. Klopfer -- to Benjamin Malzberg, 1936 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - B. Klopfer -- from Benjamin Malzberg, 1936 Oct. 21
  - Klopfer, Erna (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 15
  - Klossner, Valens E. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 7; 1p.
  - Kluckhohn, Clyde (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc: Boas, F. to Tozzer, A.M., Oct. 4, 1940)
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - (Enc: Dinner in honor of Dr. Tozzer), 1940 Oct. 7; 1p.
  - Kluge, Karl (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 end; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 1p.
  - Klugmann, N.J. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 5; 1p.
  - Klüver, H. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 2; 1p.
  - Knapp, Charles (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 3
    - C. Knapp -- to N.S. Spencer, 1911 Jan. 13; 1p.
  - Knauff, C.G.B. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 11; 1p.
  - Knauth, Antonio (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 end; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - A. Knauth -- to E.L. Boas, 1904 June 23; 1p.
  - Knauth, O. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 4; 1p.
  - Kniberg, E.C. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 18; 1p.
  - Knickerbocker Press (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 9
  - Knight, H.R. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 1; 1p.
  - Knight, Julia (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 12
  - Knopf, Alfred A. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - (Enc: Assignment of copyright), 1931 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 21; 2p.